

Zohary Andrianome

s zohary.andrianome

in linkedin.com/zohary.andrianome

zoharyandrianome@gmail.com

https://zoharyandrianome-portfolio.vercel.app/

Web and Mobile Developer

I am a motivated web and mobile application developer, striving for a constructive journey. My objectives are to constantly nurture new skills and gather experiences, meanwhile producing meticulous and great-quality of work.

My specialties are building UI interfaces, building APIs to later use them in frontend interfaces,

and implementing tests and pipelines to ensure good practices are respected.

Education

2016 - 2019

BCs Degree in Software Engineering University of Technology of Mauritius

2012 - 2016

Diploma in Chemical and Renewable Energy Engineering University of Mauritius

2011

Baccalauréat Général Série Scientifique Les Ecoles BIRD, Antananarivo, Madagascar

Cognitive traits

Team worker
Fast learner
Used to work under pressure
Great communication skills

Languages

English French Malagasy

Work Experience and Main roles

Web Application Developer - Remote

June 2022 - Current

Exponent.ch - Switzerland

- Translating Figma mock-ups into web interfaces
- Integrating API endpoints into web application UI using GraphQL
- Upgrading existing apps to the latest NextJS and applying recommended best pratices
- Implementing tests with Playwright
- Implementing CI for web applications
- Customizing ERPNext/Frappe projects into specific client needs

Consultant, Web Developer - Remote

December 2020 - Current

Maasil Inc - Antananarivo, Madagascar

- Translating mock-ups into web and mobile interfaces
- Developing API endpoints for browser and mobile platforms
- Integrating API endpoints into the user interface
- Building reusable UI components
- Ensuring browser and mobile compatibility of applications
- Implementing tracking features

ReactJs & AngularJS Front-end Developer

October 2021 - July 2023

Astek - Antananarivo, Madagascar

- Developing front-end interfaces with reusable UI components
- Integrating API endpoints into the user interface
- Resolving existing bugs in existing projects
- Implementing new features in existing projects

ReactJs & NodeJs Developer - Remote Freelancer

May 2021 - July 2021

ESA - Antananarivo, Madagascar

- Developing the school public website and back-office management system
- Creating the database structure using FireBase
- Creating all API endpoints using ExpressJS and Heroku
- Integrating API endpoints into the ReactIs user interface
- Deploying front-end and back-end applications

NextJs Developer - Remote

April 2021 - December 2021

Opcadia - Lyon, France

- Building front-end interfaces and features with reusable UI components
- Ensuring browser and mobile compatibility of applications
- Implementing tracking features
- \bullet $\,$ Optimizing current projects for better SEO and better LightHouse score
- Integrating 3rd party CMS content into Nextjs application

VueJs Frontend Developer - Part time

November 2020

Inforce Madagascar, Antananarivo

- Building front-end interfaces and features
- Integrating API endpoints into the VueJS application
- Ensuring browser and mobile compatibility of applications
- Implementing payment feature using Stripe in Vuels

Frontend Developer - Remote

July 2020 - November 2020 Esokia Web Agency, Mauritius

- Building and styling front-end templates
 - Ensuring browser and mobile compatibility of applications

ReactJs Developer - Remote

May 2020 - September 2020

Datadict Ltd, Paris, France

- Building front-end interfaces and features with reusable components
- Integrating API endpoints into the ReactJs UI
- Ensuring browser and mobile compatibility of applications
- Implementing payment feature using Stripe in ReactIs

Web Developer and Designer - Remote

April 2020 - September 2020

Sedeco Ltd, Mauritius

- · Building front-end interfaces and dynamic features
- Creating website mock-ups with Photoshop CS6

Front-end Developer and Integrator - Internship

December 2018 - August 2019 Esokia Web Agency, Mauritius